timesofoman.com 2013-12-19

# Times of Oman :: Privacy

---  
  
Fri, Jan 31, 2020

  * Weather
  * |   
---  

Max |  : |     
Min |  : |     
Sunrise |  : |     
Sunset |  : |     
Humidity |  : |     
  
  * Prayer Time
  * Fajar |  : |  05.23 am   
---|---|---  
Dhuhr |  : |  12.09 pm   
Asar |  : |  03:09 pm   
Magrib |  : |  05.29 pm   
Isha |  : |  06.45 pm   
  * Oil Price
  *   * Gold Price
  * **Price in RO**  
  
---  
24ct / gm |  : |  15.40   
22ct / gm |  : |  15.00   

  * Currency Rates
  * **Forex Rates vs R01**  
  
---  
US Dollar |  : |  2.58   
Euro |  : |  1.87   
Pound |  : |  1.58   
Indian Rs. |  : |  159.82   
Pak Rs. |  : |  274.73   
Bangla Taka |  : |  198.81   

| 

  * **Times of Oman** recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of information and will keep the information you entrust to us safely and securely. 

**What this Privacy Policy Covers**  
This policy tells you how Times of Oman collects information from you, how we protect it and how we use it, and share all personal information which you provide when you use any of Times of Oman sites (the "Sites"), unless otherwise specified on the relevant site where a different privacy policy will be displayed This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Times of Oman does not own or control or to people that Times of Oman does not employ or manage. 

**Information Collection and Use**  
We respect each visitor's right to personal privacy. To that end, we collect and use information throughout our web site only as disclosed in this Privacy Policy. This statement applies solely to the information collected on [timesofoman.com](http://timesofoman.com/). 

We will collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways including directly from you when you register on the Sites, use other Times of Oman services, enter competitions or prize draws, navigate around our Sites or respond to communications from us. Times of Oman may also receive personally identifiable information from, third parties including our related companies, our business partners and publicly available sources of information. 

The following is what we normally collect about you to help us provide you with our services, where we can:   
• Personal attributes, name, address, gender, date of birth, email, telephone number, and service details;   
• Information on how you use our website, including details of your domain name and Internet Protocol address, operating system, browser, cookies, time spent on a page or content, and the route you took to navigate through the pages;   
• Other data, from time to time, to help us provide you with improved products and services. 

If you choose not to provide us with certain information we may not be able to provide you with a particular service.   
Times of Oman also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Times of Oman! cookie information and the page you requested. 

In addition, when you use Times of Oman's services, you may make some of your personal information public. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return and Times of Oman will not be responsible for the use or misuse of such information. The main uses of your personal information are to verify your identity; to help provide our services; to administer those services; to enable us to review and improve our service to provide access to certain areas of the website; to personalise your visit to our site; to run competitions and games and to assist with advertising and other revenue generation functions. 

  * The information we collect is also used to notify visitors about events, changes and other information about this web site. The information we collect is never shared with other organizations for commercial or other purposes.   
This information may be used for marketing (where you have agreed to this) and for market research purposes, including internal demographic studies, to provide, optimise and personalise our services and to send you newsletters and information (where you have agreed to this) about our products and services.   
We may use information about you to create a picture of your interests. This will allow us to understand our customers and visitors better, so we can make our services and marketing more relevant. Information that we use in this way may include:   
(i) information about your use of this and other Times of Oman Sites;   
(ii) household classification data,   
(iii) your responses to communications from us;   
(iv) your interaction with other parts of the Times of Oman Group;   
(v) information you provide when you register on a Site;   
(vi) customer surveys;   
(vii) information provided by other companies, where you gave them permission to share this information. We may use a variety of technical methods such as cookies and web beacons to collate this information (see the section below on "Use of Cookies" for further information). 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**  
Times of Oman will NOT disclose personally identifiable information about you to third parties except in the following situations:   
• We have your consent to share the information;   
• We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;   
• We need to share the information with certain service partners in order to respond to your comments or to resolve service issues. (Unless we tell you differently, these partners have no independent right to use this information except to respond to your comments or to resolve the service issues.);   
• We respond to requests from any Omani or foreign government, security, defence, revenue, regulatory or other authority, agency or officer;   
• We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal proceedings;   
• When required by law that such action is necessary to protect and defend the rights of property [timesofoman.com](http://timesofoman.com/);   
• When applicable law or regulation requires disclosure of information to protect the safety or security of users of our Sites;   
• We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Times of Oman Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services;   
• If we use third party processors to administer and process your personal information for the purposes notified in the Privacy Policy, e.g. for hosting activities related to the use of our Sites or services; or   
• We may need to share details with third parties (such as auditors or legal advisors) to obtain advice. Any such processing will be governed by an agreement in the form required by law, preserving any statutory data protection rights. 

  * **Who has access to the information at** **Times of Oman?**   
We may share your information with other members of the Times of Oman Group. As used in this Privacy Policy the Times of Oman Group includes Muscat Press & Publishing House SAOC, and all of its subsidiary and affiliated entities, including companies such as those branded under Muscat Press & Publishing House SAOC. In this Privacy Policy "we", "us", "our" and "ourselves" means any member of this Group.   
People we may disclose your personal information will include:   
• Members of Muscat Press & Publishing House SAOC;   
• our related companies;   
• advertisers and content partners, either in an aggregate form eg. "5,000 users clicked on a banner ad";   
• credit-reporting and fraud-checking agencies;   
• our professional advisers, including our accountants, auditors and lawyers;   
• other telecommunication and information service providers;   
• by disclosing individual records such as IP addresses as may be required by law; or   
• government and regulatory authorities and other organisations, as required or authorised by law.   
We will ensure that these people only use such information to perform the above functions, and that they have adequate procedures in place to deal with your data securely. Some of these people may be based outside Oman. 

**Use of information for marketing**  
In line with any permission you give us, we may send you direct marketing about our own, or carefully selected third parties' goods and services and disclose your information to other organisations that may send direct marketing to you. You can change your marketing preferences if you are registered with us. In addition, you can unsubscribe from email communications via unsubscribe links provided in communications sent to you. 

**Link from or to Other Sites**  
As a means of providing useful resources to our users, [timesofoman.com](http://timesofoman.com/) provides links to other web sites. We try to carefully choose web sites that we believe are useful and meet our high standards. However, because web sites can change so quickly, we do not guarantee the standards of any website links we provide nor do we imply endorsement. [timesofoman.com](http://timesofoman.com/) is not responsible for the data and privacy policies, content or security of other websites that are linked to our site. . You should be aware that when you are on our Sites you could be directed to other sites where the personal information collected is outside of our control. The privacy policy of the new site will govern the information obtained from you on that site. 

**Access to your account information**  
You can access and change the information that you provided during registration. Simply click on this link [http://www.timesofoman.com](http://www.timesofoman.com/) and then log in with your member name and password wherever necessary. There are instructions on the start page to help you recover your password if you've forgotten it. You can also contact us via e-mail by clicking "Contact Us" bar of [timesofoman.com](http://www.timesofoman.com/) page, or send an email directly to [webeditor@timesofoman.com](mailto:webeditor@timesofoman.com). Please include information in the e-mail that will help us identify your account so we can assist you with your inquiry or request. 

  * **Cookies**   
We collect information through technology to make our Sites and other content or services which we make available to you more interesting and useful to you. For instance, when you come to one of our Sites via your computer or other media device, we may combine your visitor session information or other information collected through cookies, web beacons and other technical methods with personally identifiable information in order to understand and improve your online experiences and to determine what products, promotions and services you prefer or are likely to be of interest to you.   
Cookies are pieces of information that a Site sends to your computer or other media device while you are viewing or interacting with the Site. We use cookies for a variety of purposes including tracking usage on our Sites in order to- enhance our guests' experience on our Sites and to learn more about your preferences and interests   
Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on the pages of Sites. We also use these technical methods to analyse the traffic patterns on our Sites, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of our Sites.   
Times of Oman ensures that all information collected and accessed by Times of Oman through the access of these cookies will be maintained in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Times of Oman allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Times of Oman 's cookies. 

**Security**  
We take various precautions to keep your personal information secure from unauthorized access and will store your personal information for so long as it is necessary to provide you our services or for archive purposes. You are responsible for keeping your User ID and password secure and you should not disclose them to anyone. 

**Notification of Changes**  
Times of Oman may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time and we will post the latest version on this and all our other Sites. If we ever wish to use your personal information in a way which is incompatible with the information in this Privacy Policy, we will only do so with your consent. 

**Acceptance of Privacy Policy**  
Your right to access this website is conditional upon your full acceptance of this Privacy Policy and by accessing the Sites you signify your consent that we store and process your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Contact Us**  
If you need further assistance or have queries about our use of personal information, please send us an email with your questions or comments to [webeditor@timesofoman.com](mailto:webeditor@timesofoman.com)

* * *

|  |   
---|---  
|   
|  | 

######  Thursday \- [MORE](http://www.timesofoman.com/NewsSection/Thursday.aspx)  
  
---  

by Saleh Al Shaibany

The thing to remember is that depression paralyses your life and causes a lot of anxiety to your fam...  
  
---  

| 

######  Travel \- [MORE](http://www.timesofoman.com/NewsSection/Travel.aspx)  
  
---  

by Will Hawkes/The Independent

A winter’s break in the Estonian capital reveals snowy scenery, a Christmas market and small craft s...  
  
---  

|   
| 

######  Horoscope \- [MORE](http://www.timesofoman.com/NewsSection/Horoscope.aspx)  
  
---  

by Times News Service

Horoscope is a kind of "psychological map" which shows certain patterns of every individual's person...  
  
---  

| 

######  HI \- [MORE](http://www.timesofoman.com/NewsSection/HI.aspx)  
  
---  

by Hubert Vaz/Hi

Munich is a popular destination in Germany that dresses up in white for Christmas, beckoning tourist...  
  
---
